cuntwars.com 2017-12-28

# cuntwars.com Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to the following websites: cuntwars.com (collectively, the “Sites”, or individually, a “Site”).

By accessing and using our Sites, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Sites. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

The security of your Data is very important to cuntwars.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

**Data collected**

Personal Information: Non-Registered users can watch content without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However the visitor's IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.

To access the Site registration is required. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.

Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Sites. When you visit cuntwars.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. cuntwars.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.

Log File Information: When you visit cuntwars.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

**Uses**

Your Personally identifiable information submitted to cuntwars.com is used to provide to the user the website's features and special personalized features.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.

We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).

We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the cuntwars.com user-experience.

**Disclosure of information**

If under duty to do so cuntwars.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of cuntwars.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is cuntwars.com 's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

**Security**

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. cuntwars.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to cuntwars.com and you do so at your own risk.

**Notification of changes**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Sites. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use any of our Sites, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use any of our Sites after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Contact information**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your password, user name and account number so we can service you quicker.
